TOKYO DAIICHI BANK SHINJUKU BRANCH
（東京第一銀行新宿分行）
-Welcome. -Here you go.
-歡迎光臨 -麻煩了
You're here to pay the taxes?
要繳稅金嗎？
-Please take this number and wait. -Okay.
-請拿號碼牌稍候 -好的
-Wow. -Incredible.
-好厲害 -了不起
She's amazing.
她太強了
Branch Manager, the rumors about her were true.
經理，有關她的傳聞是真的
We did the right thing by calling
沒錯，我們請求總部行政支援
headquarters for administrative help.
看來是做對了
Customer with ticket number five.
號碼牌五號的客戶
Thank you very much for waiting.
謝謝您耐心等待
I wonder if she's doing okay.
不知道她還行嗎？
It was for administrative help, but I felt uneasy sending
這次是行政支援，但是我很不放心
Hanasaki out by herself.
讓花咲自己過去
I'm sure she's fine.
我相信她沒問題的
Plus, it's not an inspection.
加上這不是稽核工作
Being a teller is her calling.
當櫃員是她的天職
But Soma, aren't you lonely?
可是相馬，你不會孤單嗎？
Since you're always with Hanasaki.
你一直和花咲在一起
Lonely?
孤單？
No way! When I'm by myself,
怎麼可能？我一個人的時候
I'm so refreshed, and it reminds me how wonderful it is
神清氣爽，而且這讓我想起
to be trouble-free.
沒有麻煩的日子有多美好
What?
是嗎？
I want to go back in time to when Hanasaki wasn't here,
我想回到花咲還沒來的時候
and tell myself, "Don't take this happiness for granted."
還要告訴自己 “別把這種幸福視為理所當然”
I guess you have your own struggles.
我猜你有你的難處
-You understand? -Yes.
-你懂了？ -懂
Oh, look at the time. I have to go now.
看看時間，我得走了
-Bye. -Okay. I'm so busy.
-再見 -好，真忙啊
It's so quiet…
好安靜啊
-Thank you.
-謝謝光臨 -謝謝
We all worked hard today.
今天大家都很辛苦
-It was so busy. -Yeah.
-好忙呀 -是啊
I forgot how fun it is to be a teller.
我都忘了當櫃員有多開心
Put your hands up!
手都舉起來！
Move, and he'll die!
要是敢動，他就死定了
What… bank robbery?
銀行搶劫？
I told you to put your hands up!
我叫妳把手舉起來！
-Hey you! -Yes.
-喂，你！ -是
Put the cash in here.
把現金放進袋子裡
-Give me all the cash you have! -Yes!
-把所有現金都給我！ -是
Hurry up and get to it!
動作快
Here. This is all we have right now.
來了，現在就只有這些
-Let's go. -Okay.
-我們走 -好
Oh! My arm. It's broken.
我的手臂折到了！
Ouch.
好痛！
Hold up!
等一下，這群混蛋！
Ms. Hanasaki! Wait! Where are you going?
花咲小姐，等等，妳要做什麼？
Please move. I have to throw this at them!
請讓開，我要去丟他們
Wait. This is training!
等等，這是演習！
Who cares if it's training.
誰管什麼演習啊！
Training?
演習？
What?
啊？
What? So the bank robbers are…
所以搶匪是…
They're from the police.
他們是警察
-Section Chief Fushimi. -Yes?
-伏見課長 -是
You didn't tell Ms. Hanasaki?
你沒告訴花咲小姐嗎？
I'm so sorry.
對不起
I forgot since it was so busy this morning.
早上太忙，我忘了
It was training…
是演習啊…
I'm so sorry.
真抱歉
TOKYO DAIICHI BANK HEADQUARTERS
（東京第一銀行總部）
Hello, Chairman Itami.
伊丹會長，讓您久等了
Thank you.
謝謝
CHAIRMAN OF ITAMI GROUP SEIGO ITAMI
（伊丹集團會長，伊丹清吾）
ITAMI GROUP
（伊丹集團）
GINZA REDEVELOPMENT PROJECT
（銀座再開發計畫，業務概要）
PLANNED OPENING - FALL 2019
（預定於2019年秋開幕）
Chairman Itami, this plan is finally taking off.
伊丹會長，終於要啟動
The Ginza Redevelopment Project.
銀座再開發計畫了
Over 200 shops, restaurants,
超過兩百間商店、餐廳
hotels, offices, theatres, and art museums.
旅館、辦公室、戲院與美術館
Once it's completed, it will be the nation's biggest cultural facility.
一旦落成，將是全日本最大的 綜合文化設施
We expect to see 50 million customers a year.
每年預計吸引五千萬名顧客
With more people, Ginza will change too.
有了更多顧客，銀座也會改變
Wonderful.
太好了
Our budget is no less than 300 billion yen.
預算不會低於三千億日圓
Our bank would love
敝銀行很樂意
to help you out in that regard.
在這方面提供協助
Of course, I want Tokyo Daiichi Bank to lend us a hand
當然，我希望東京第一銀行
by being the coordinator.
協助我們統籌協調
Please take the lead.
可以的話，請你們主導了
Thank you.
非常感謝
But please go easy on the interest rate.
不過利息上請放寬
We will do our best to meet your expectations.
我們會盡力達成期望
I use this bank
這間銀行
for both work and private use.
公私兩方面我都使用
I hear great things about your son Mr. Seiichiro.
令公子清一郎先生 我聽說不少關於他在新宿分行
-His work at the Shinjuku Branch. -Oh, please don't mention it.
-優秀的表現 -請別提了
I want him to gain knowledge
我要他趁在這裡工作時
about management while he works here.
學習管理方面的經驗
Eventually, he'll be taking my place.
他終究要接我的位子
That's an incredible plan. We look forward to
那真是了不起的計畫，我們非常期待
working together in the future.
未來一起合作
Thank you.
感謝
Likewise.
我也一樣
He finally made it clear that he'll use us as the coordinating bank.
他終於明說要我們成為主要銀行
Yeah.
對
Mr. Shindo, your time has finally come.
真藤本部長，您的時代終於到了
There is one thing
有一件事
I need to let you know.
需要讓您知道
What is it?
什麼事？
Hanasaki from Branch Inspection
稽核班的花咲
is at the Shinjuku Branch for administrative support.
正在新宿分行做行政支援
What?
什麼？
Thankfully, it's only today and tomorrow.
幸好只有今明兩天
Chairman Itami's son is in the Finance Department,
伊丹會長的公子在融資課
so I'm sure they won't have a chance to meet but I did alert
我相信他們沒有機會碰面 不過為了安全起見
Section Chief Haneda just to be safe.
我特別提醒羽田課長
Hopefully, nothing happens.
希望不會有事情發生
Not "hopefully"!
不是“希望”
Prevent it!
要全力防止！
There's a chance that this project will go down the drain
要是伊丹會長生氣，這個計畫
if Chairman Itami becomes upset.
有可能付諸流水
The Ginza Redevelopment Project
銀座再開發計畫
will be a 100-billion-yen contract for this bank.
對這個銀行將是一千億日圓的合約
It's our chance to get ahead of our rival, Hakusui Bank.
是我們超越競爭對手白水銀行的機會
We will not let go of this chance!
絕對不能放過這個機會
Yes, sir.
是！
Everything is balanced. Thank you.
結帳明細無誤，大家辛苦了
Thank you.
辛苦了
Sorry for causing a scene just now.
抱歉剛剛引起騷動
It's only natural since you didn't know.
妳不知道，那很自然
Yes! Branch Manager was shaking,
就是啊，經理在發抖
and Ms. Yasukawa looked close to tears.
還有安川小姐看起來都快哭了
I never imagined that it was just training.
我怎麼也想不到那只是演習
I knew it was training but it was still really scary.
我知道是演習，可是還是很嚇人
I know! Those police officers are such good actors.
就是啊，那些警察演技真好
Yeah.
對呀
Can you process this?
妳可以處理這個嗎？
Who is he?
這個人是誰？
Mr. Itami from the Finance Department.
融資課的伊丹先生
-Um… -Excuse me.
-那個… -抱歉
We are done for today.
我們今天工作結束了
-So what? -We can't process this now.
-那又怎麼樣？ -現在無法處理
It's still working hours, right?
現在還是上班時間，不是嗎？
Doing this tomorrow will be a hassle.
明天做會很麻煩
I know you guys want to go home early,
我知道你們想早一點下班
but we at the Finance Department work overtime every day,
但是我們融資課每天加班
so it's selfish to do things at your own convenience.
妳們方便時才做很自私
Um…
那個
With all due respect…
恕我直言
we're not just trying to leave early.
我們並沒有想早下班
What?
怎樣？
We have to scrap everything and recalculate.
我們必須作廢後再重新計算
We have to balance everything again.
所有東西必須再結算一次
Do you understand that?
你了解嗎？
Please take this back overnight.
這個請拿回去
-Come back tomorrow-- -Hey.
-明天再拿來 -喂
Who are you?
妳是哪位？
I'm Hanasaki from Branch Inspection.
我是總部稽核班的花咲
-I'm here for two days-- -Ms. Hanasaki.
-我來這裡兩天… -花咲小姐
Can you stop being so uptight?
妳可以別這麼固執嗎？
Do you know how much money we handle at the Finance Department?
妳知道我們融資課經手多少錢嗎？
It's nothing like the coins you handle at the window.
可不像妳們在櫃檯經手的零錢
You'll do this for me, right Section Chief Fushimi?
你會幫我處理吧，伏見課長？
Oh… well…
那個…
What's wrong, Itami?
怎麼了，伊丹？
Section Chief Haneda,
羽田課長，你評評理
this lady from the headquarters
總部來的這位小姐
won't process my checks.
不肯處理我的支票
You're Ms. Hanasaki from Branch Inspection?
妳是稽核班的花咲小姐嗎？
Yes.
是
You may not understand,
妳可能不了解
but unlike the carefree Sales Division,
融資課和悠閒的營業課不同
the Finance Department has lots of work to do.
融資課的工作非常重
We can't work if you get mad over one or two checks.
要是妳們為了一、兩張支票生氣 我們無法工作
-Please do this, Mr. Fushimi. -I understand.
-伏見課長，麻煩你處理 -我了解
That's settled.
問題解決了
Thanks,
請多關照囉
Ms. Hanasaki.
花咲小姐
Who is that guy named Itami anyway? He's so arrogant!
那個伊丹到底是什麼人？也太傲慢了
He's full of himself and looks down on others.
自以為是，瞧不起人
He gets me so mad!
他惹得我好生氣
It's also annoying.
而且很討厭的是
-Him being good looking. -Right?
-他長得真帥 -對吧？
Mr. Itami is always causing us trouble.
伊丹先生總是找我們麻煩
-I can see that. -Okay.
-我看得出來 -很好
Now that you've released your stress,
既然妳們已經釋放壓力了
try our daily special.
嚐嚐我們的每日特色菜吧
It's Kabocha chakinshibori.
這是南瓜茶巾絞
-It looks delicious. -Here.
-看起來好好吃 -給妳
Thank you very much.
謝謝
Thank you.
我開動了
By the way, why is he so arrogant?
對了，他為什麼那麼傲慢呢？
He's still young.
他還年輕
He's the heir to the Itami Group.
他是伊丹集團的繼承人
-Itami-- -The Itami Group is that company.
-伊丹… -伊丹集團是那間
The one that builds huge buildings and hotels?
蓋那些巨大建築物和旅館的公司嗎？
The chairman's only son
對，他們會長的獨生子
works at our branch.
在我們分行做事
-Only son-- -He's the only son.
-獨生子？ -如果他是獨生子
He's the heir, right?
他就是唯一繼承人，對吧？
He's working at our branch to learn about business in order to
他來我們分行工作為的是了解業務
take over the Itami Group.
好接管伊丹集團
Mai, if you get that son, you'll be filthy rich.
舞，要是妳和他在一起，妳會超有錢
You'll be the president's wife.
妳會成為會長夫人
Though your dream to be a banker's wife won't come true.
不過妳成為銀行員妻子的夢想 就無法實現了
Like I said, I never dreamed of that before.
我說了，我從來沒有過那種夢想
And leave us alone. We're having a girl's talk.
而且別打擾我們，我們在聊姊妹話題
-There's a wall here. -Fine, fine.
-這裡有一面牆 -好…
What's this about the banker's wife?
銀行員妻子是怎麼回事？
It's nothing at all. It's all his imagination.
沒有，那全是他的想像
What? Itami junior is at the Shinjuku Branch?
什麼，伊丹少東在新宿分行？
It slipped my mind.
我沒留意
If I'd known, I wouldn't have let Hanasaki go by herself.
我要是知道就不會讓花咲自己去
You're worrying too much. Even Hanasaki wouldn't…
你擔心過頭了，就算是花咲也不會…
But apparently, she already had an issue with junior.
可是她顯然已經和少東爭執過了
Wow, Hanasaki.
不愧是花咲
Mr. Kodama contacted me and told me to be more careful.
兒玉次長找過我，要我多加注意
What is she doing?
她在搞什麼啊？
I'm so worried,
我好擔心
that I can barely eat.
擔心到快吃不下了
I see…
這樣啊
Yes?
怎麼？
The Itami Group is planning
事實上，伊丹集團正在制訂
the Ginza Redevelopment Project, and our bank is about to be chosen
銀座再開發計畫 我們銀行就要被選為
as the coordinating bank.
主要銀行
The person pushing for that
推動這件事的
is General Manager Shindo.
是真藤本部長
I just got a bad feeling.
我突然有不好的感覺
-Right? -Yes.
-對吧？ -對
It doesn't matter whose son he is. What's wrong is wrong.
不管他是誰的兒子，錯就是錯
I know. But the management are all scared of him.
是啊，但是所有主管都怕他
Everyone calls him "VIP" or "in charge."
大家叫他“貴賓” 或是“碰不得的保管物”
VIP…
貴賓啊…
Then he always had that
那麼他一向都是那種
arrogant and haughty attitude?
傲慢自大的態度嗎？
Yeah, ever since he came.
沒錯，從他來了之後都是那個樣子
Year-end party?
尾牙？
-I'll pass. -But…
-我不去 -可是
Usually everyone attends.
通常每個人都會參加
I don't plan to be here for long,
我沒打算在這裡待很久
and I don't want to
而且我不想
become friends with all of you.
和你們任何人交朋友
He'll say that he's cut above
他會面無表情地說
the rest of the employees, with a straight face.
他比其他人高出一等
There's an error on here,
這裡有個錯誤
so can you re-do this please?
麻煩你重寫
What? Just go and fix it yourself.
妳自己改掉就好了
We can't do that.
我們不能改
I'll leave these small funds up to you.
這種小錢就由妳決定吧
He thinks everything aside from loans is a menial job.
他認為融資以外的工作都很卑賤
Everything about him is awful.
關於他，沒一句好話
Yeah.
就是啊
Even if he's connected to one of our clients,
就算他和我們的顧客有關係
it's wrong.
也不能夠讓他
-He can't do whatever he wants, right? -But…
-為所欲為吧？ -可是
He's apparently pretty good working with loans.
他顯然對放貸很有一套
He brings in lots of new, big loan contracts.
他簽了很多新的大型貸款合約
Really?
真的嗎？
People say that it's because
大家說那是因為
those companies are connected with the Itami Group
那些公司和伊丹集團有關聯
and he has connections.
而且他有人脈
That doesn't justify everything.
那也不能合理化所有事情
Therefore, please go to the Shinjuku Branch tomorrow.
所以，明天請你去新宿分行
-What do you mean? -Well.
-什麼意思？ -就是說
Just keep an eye on her.
只要盯住她就好
Soma, you're the only one that can stop Hanasaki.
相馬，你是唯一能阻止花咲的人
Give me a break.
你饒了我吧？
I was looking forward to relaxing.
我原本還很期待明天
-To having trouble-free day tomorrow. -Please.
-又能輕鬆沒麻煩的 -拜託你了
Director Karashima was worried too.
其實辛島部長也很擔心
Plus, you've worked at the Shinjuku Branch before.
再說你在新宿分行待過啊
That was ten years ago.
那是十年前的事了
Please do me this one favor.
請你幫我這個忙
This week is Customer Satisfaction Improvement Week.
這個星期是客戶滿意度改善週
Please work with the customer's
請將客戶滿意度
satisfaction as your priority.
當成優先工作項目
Next on our topic is…
下一個主題是…
Why is Mr. Soma here?
為什麼相馬先生會在這裡？
I follow orders from the boss.
我遵從上司的指示
That's what a businessman does.
那就是識時務者所為
What?
什麼？
So you came all the way here to keep an eye on me?
所以你是專程來盯我的嗎？
I didn't want to come either.
我也不想來
They don't trust me at all.
他們一點都不信任我
Well, you already caused trouble yesterday, right?
妳昨天已經惹麻煩了，對吧？
I didn't cause trouble… oh yeah,
我沒有惹麻煩…說到這個
listen to this Mr. Soma. This guy is horrible--
相馬先生，你聽我說 那個傢伙很可惡…
Stop. That's enough. Listen, Hanasaki,
停！夠了，聽好花咲
I've told you over and over again.
我一再告訴過妳
-Be quiet, even if you want to speak up. -Yes.
-就算有想說的，也先閉上嘴 -是
But do you ever listen
可是這個忠告
to that advice, even once? No.
妳有聽進去過一次嗎？沒有
I have, two or three times.
有兩、三次吧？
I'll say it even stronger this time with maximum effort.
這次妳得更堅決，妳要用最大努力
Don't say anything unnecessary.
別說多餘的話！
Oh, he's here.
他來了
That's Itami junior?
那就是惡名昭彰的伊丹少東？
Yeah.
對
Good morning.
早安
-Oh, you're Ms. Hanasaki? -Yes.
-妳是花咲？ -是
Smile.
微笑
I'm Soma from Branch Inspection.
我是總部稽核班的相馬
Hello.
你好
Then you're Ms. Hanasaki's boss?
那麼你是花咲小姐的上司囉？
Yes.
是
She's really loud, so please keep her in check.
這個人很吵，請你管一下她
Um… you don't need to say…
你沒有必要說…
Okay.
好的
Please do your best.
請你盡力而為
Why does he look down on people like that?
他為什麼那樣瞧不起人？
Smile, Mr. Soma.
相馬先生，微笑
This is not good, Mr. Karashima.
辛島部長，這可不好
I hear that Hanasaki caused trouble with
我聽說花咲給伊丹會長兒子
Chairman Itami's son.
帶來不少麻煩
I'm very sorry.
非常抱歉
It seems to have been a small issue,
那似乎只是一件小事
but I sent her boss, Mr. Soma,
不過為了以防萬一
to the Shinjuku Branch just in case.
我派她的上司相馬先生去新宿分行
You know about that
你知道
Ginza Redevelopment Project by the Itami Group, that I'm heading, right?
伊丹集團的銀座再開發計畫 是我在領導吧？
Of course.
當然
I hear that our bank will become the coordinator.
聽說我們銀行會是主要銀行
But it's not confirmed yet,
但是事情尚未塵埃落定
so we can't let our guard down.
所以我們不能鬆懈下來
We want to avoid
和伊丹集團
even the smallest of issues with the Itami Group.
就算是任何小問題都要避免
Both with the chairman himself,
對於會長本人
and his son.
還有他兒子都要
But Hanasaki
可是到目前為止
has never done anything wrong up until now.
花咲並沒有做過任何錯事
She is only doing her job.
她只是做她的工作
I'm not concerned about what's
我不在乎
right or wrong.
事情的對或錯
What do you mean?
這是什麼意思呢？
What's important is thinking about what is most beneficial
重要的是思考怎麼做
for Tokyo Daiichi Bank.
對東京第一銀行最有益處
I'm opening a savings account for my newborn grandchild.
我要幫我剛出生的孫子開儲蓄帳戶
Is that right? Congratulations.
是這樣嗎？恭喜您
We will take good care of it.
我們會仔細處理的
She becomes a different person once she wears a uniform.
她穿上櫃員制服就變了一個人
Mr. Koda.
幸田先生
Long time no see. How are you?
好久不見，您好嗎？
Mr. Soma.
相馬先生
You came back to the Shinjuku Branch?
你回新宿分行了？
I'm at headquarters now. I'm here for support.
我現在在總部，我是來支援的
I see. I'm glad to hear that.
原來如此，太好了
I never thought I'd get to see you today.
我沒想到今天會見到你
Thank you for continuing to use our bank.
謝謝你仍選擇與我們銀行合作
-Thank you. -But ours is just a small company.
-感謝 -不過我們只是個小公司
Don't say that.
別那麼說
Welcome, Mr. Koda.
幸田先生，歡迎
Hello, Section Chief Fushimi. I brought this.
你好，伏見課長，我帶了這個來
Please enjoy it.
請大家享用
-Thank you so much. -Not at all.
-一直以來承蒙您關照了 -不會
-Who are you seeing today? -I'm heading to Finance.
-今天有什麼事呢？ -我要去融資課
Okay.
這樣啊
-Bye. -Goodbye.
-再見
Mr. Soma, you know him?
相馬先生認識他嗎？
Yes, when I worked at this branch ten years ago,
對，十年前我在這裡工作時
I was in charge of Koda Sangyo's loans.
幸田產業的貸款是我負責的
Oh, I see.
原來是這樣
He's such a nice man.
真是個好客戶
Yes.
是啊
Mr. Itami.
伊丹先生
Mr. Koda.
幸田先生
Is everything all right?
都還好嗎？
You don't look well…
你臉色不太好
Well…
這個嘛…
it's hard for me to bring this up,
真難啟齒
but my loan request is in danger.
不過我的貸款申請不太順利
Really?
真的嗎？
I've had it with Mr. Itami.
我不想再和伊丹先生談了
Itami…
伊丹…
I'm sorry for complaining to you.
抱歉，還找你抱怨
No problem.
沒事
-I'll be leaving. -Goodbye.
-我走了 -慢走
Everything is balanced. Thank you very much.
結帳明細無誤，大家辛苦了
Thank you.
辛苦了
Ms. Hanasaki, thank you so much for the last two days!
花咲小姐，這兩天謝謝妳了
Thank you.
謝謝
We're so glad you came.
真高興妳來了
You were a good example for our tellers.
妳是我們櫃員的好榜樣
Oh, please.
請別這麼說
-I learned so much. -Thank you, Ms. Hanasaki.
-我學到很多 -謝謝妳，花咲小姐
Oh, stop it. I didn't do much.
別這樣，我沒做什麼
She's definitely getting carried away.
她肯定要得意忘形了
I'll be going now.
我先走了
Thank you.
謝謝
Oh, I forgot.
對了
Mr. Koda gave this to us. Let's all share it.
這是幸田先生送我們的 大家一起分享吧
-Oh! -What?
-啊！ -怎麼了？
Please wait a moment.
請等一下
I think you should ask the Finance Department first.
我認為你最好先問融資課
What do you mean?
怎麼了嗎？
It seems like the loan discussion
幸田產業的貸款申請
with Koda Sangyo isn't going so well.
似乎進行得不太順利
I see…
原來如此
We don't want them to say that
不能讓他們說
they couldn't deny the loan because we accepted this.
因為我們收下這個 所以他們無法拒絕貸款
-Right. -I see.
-沒錯 -我懂了
Who's in charge?
是誰負責的？
Mr. Itami.
好像是伊丹
Itami, huh…
伊丹啊…
Oh, Itami.
啊，伊丹！
We got something from Koda Sangyo.
幸田產業送了我們一些東西
-What should we do? -Huh?
-我們應該怎麼處理呢？ -啊？
It seems like there are issues with the loans
貸款的事好像有點問題
so I thought I'd ask…
所以我想我該問一下
-Just throw that away. -What?
-直接扔了吧 -什麼？
Since we most likely won't be financing that place.
既然貸款不可能通過
-That's not right… -Hanasaki.
-那麼做是不對的 -花咲
If you can't accept it,
如果你不接受
shouldn't you give it back?
不是應該還回去嗎？
How can you throw it away…
怎麼能夠扔掉呢？
Their company is of that level.
他們公司就是那個層級
Koda Sangyo is a customer that's been with us
幸田產業是和我們合作了
for the last ten years.
十年的公司
Does that matter?
那有關係嗎？
What's important is the business performance.
重要的是業績
First of all, why are you asking me about something you got from that
再說，幹嘛問我對於收到 那間小公司東西的意見？
small little company. I have no time for this.
我沒時間管這種事
That's so rude.
真是無禮
A support member from headquarters
從總部來支援的人
has the right to tell me how to do my job?
有資格告訴我怎麼做事嗎？
No, we do not.
我們沒有資格
I thought so.
我也這麼想
I will stop by Mr. Koda's company on the way back.
我會在回去的路上 順便拜訪幸田先生的公司
Thank you very much.
那就謝謝你了
-I'm so mad.
-真火大
-We were thinking the same thing. -Yes, we were.
-我們想著同樣的事 -對，同樣的
It must be something
能讓相馬先生火大
for you to get mad, Mr. Soma.
可見真的太過分了
Yeah.
是啊
-I see. -I'm sorry we can't.
-我知道了 -很抱歉，我們無法接受
-Can't accept your kindness. -Don't worry.
-您的好意 -別擔心
I'm sorry for causing you trouble in the end.
抱歉最後造成你的麻煩
Please sit down.
請坐
I really don't know what to do.
我實在不知道該怎麼辦
Mr. Koda.
幸田先生
I heard that it's difficult to get the loan,
我聽說要取得貸款不容易
but what did the Finance Department tell you?
但是融資課是怎麼跟你說的？
They said it's impossible with our business performance.
他們說以我們的業績是不可能的
How much is the loan?
貸款金額是？
Fifty million yen.
五千萬
Pardon me for being rude,
請原諒我這麼問
but are you in the red?
你們在赤字狀態嗎？
No. Our profits are small but we're in the black.
不是，我們獲利少，但是沒有赤字
Please look at this.
請看這個
Thank you.
好的
We have lots of orders this term, so our sales will go up
我們這一期訂單很多 所以銷售額會上升
but we'll be making more purchases as well.
但是我們也要採購更多東西
I see.
了解
This has never happened before.
以前從來沒發生過這種事
This is the first contract with Mr. Itami,
這是我第一次和伊丹先生訂契約
but I didn't think he'd be reluctant.
沒想到他會這麼不願意
When do you need it by?
最遲什麼時候需要呢？
Next Tuesday.
下星期二
-That's in four days. -Yes.
-那就是四天內 -對
What if you can't get the loan by then?
萬一到時拿不到貸款呢？
What will happen?
會出什麼事？
Our check will bounce,
我們的支票就會跳票
so we may go bankrupt.
可能因此破產
Bankrupt…
破產…
What did Itami say?
伊丹怎麼說？
He said it can't be helped even if
他說就算我們破產
we are to go bankrupt.
那也是沒辦法的事
We're not in the red,
我們沒有赤字
and there's prospect of growth.
而且有成長的前景
But
不過
I have to protect this company.
我必須保護這間公司
I'll go back one more time…
我會再去一次
No, I'll go back until I can get a loan.
不，我會再去，直到拿到貸款為止
RESTAURANT HANASAKI
（花咲居酒屋）
I wonder what will happen to the loan for Koda Sangyo.
我想知道幸田產業的貸款會怎樣
They should be able to get it with those numbers.
以那些數字，他們應該能拿到
But it's Mr. Itami.
可是有那個伊丹先生在
Whether it's approved or denied, loans require
貸款不論通不通過
many people to assess the approval.
都需要很多人評估
Even if Itami makes the wrong decision,
就算伊丹做了錯誤決定
his boss would make sure to fix it.
他的上司也一定會改正過來
You're right.
你說的對
And if their check bounces,
要是他們的支票跳票
it will make the branch look bad.
會讓分行難看
It'll cause trouble.
那會造成麻煩
So I'm sure they want to avoid that.
我相信他們會避免的
Oh no…
不好
If this continues, I might be in the red this month.
照這樣下去，我這個月可能會赤字
-What? -It's difficult.
-什麼？ -雖然這是一間
Managing a business,
私人的小居酒屋
even a small private restaurant.
經營起來也很不容易
Well, a lot of people stay home during the rainy season.
雨季很多人都待在家裡
But don't worry.
不過別擔心
Because the cuisine here is exceptionally delicious.
因為這裡的菜特別好吃
Mr. Soma, you always say such nice things.
相馬先生，你總是說好話
-It's just the truth. -That just made me feel better.
-我只是說真話 -讓我好過多了
This girl over there.
這個女兒都不會
-She gives no words of encouragement. -Not true.
-給我一句鼓勵的話 -才不是那樣
If only she would marry a rich man so that I can rest a little.
要是她能嫁個有錢人就好了 我就可以輕鬆一點
Don't expect too much.
別期望太多
I wonder if I should be happy
我在想有人願意要她
to have anyone take her.
我是不是就應該很高興？
I just prefer him to be the second born son.
我只是寧願這個女婿
Someone who can drink,
是能喝酒
enjoy talking about food,
喜歡聊食物
and go on hot-spring trips together.
和一起參加溫泉旅行的人
That would be the best.
那樣就最好了
You're so picky.
你真挑剔
He has high expectations.
他的期望很高
FROM PRESIDENT KODA OF KODA SANGYO
（幸田產業的幸田社長留言）
HE WANTS YOU TO CONTACT HIM REGARDING THE LOAN
（請回覆他談貸款的事）
FOUR DAYS LATER
（四天後）
This is Chairman Itami, huh?
這是伊丹會長啊？
He's very distinguished.
他真是傑出
He's the head of a very big company.
他是一個超大公司的負責人
This reminds me of that idiot son, and that's getting me mad.
一想到他的笨蛋兒子就讓人生氣
Hey, calm down.
喂，冷靜
Branch Inspection.
是，這裡是稽核班
Mr. Koda.
幸田先生
What's wrong?
怎麼了嗎？
What…
什麼？
Your loan was denied?
你的貸款被拒絕了？
-Let's go to Koda Sangyo first. -Okay.
-先去幸田產業 -是
What? You were denied today?
你是今天才被拒絕的？
But you needed it by today, right?
但是你今天需要資金，對吧？
I couldn't get in touch with him for two days.
沒錯，我兩天都聯絡不上他
He wasn't at the branch today,
他今天不在分行裡
and I finally got him on the phone a while ago.
不久前，我終於跟他通上電話
What do you mean, Mr. Itami?
伊丹先生，這是什麼意思？
You didn't hear me?
你沒聽到嗎？
I told you that we're denying your loan this time.
我說這次我們拒絕貸款給你
Please wait.
請等一下
Why are you telling me this now?
你為什麼現在才告訴我？
Everything at a bank requires approval.
銀行的事都需要批准
There's nothing I can do on my own.
我沒辦法自己決定
Thirty million yen,
三千萬就好
even 20 million yen is enough. Please!
甚至兩千萬也夠，拜託了
Please!
拜託了
That's horrible.
太可惡了
What do you plan to do?
你打算怎麼辦？
I have to prepare 50 million yen for now
我必須在跳票之前
before our payment check bounces.
準備五千萬日圓
But getting 50 million by today is…
但是今天要籌到五千萬…
I'm asking everyone, from my acquaintances to customers
從熟人到客戶，每一個人我都問
and begging for their help.
求他們幫忙
Mr. Sakamoto?
坂本先生？
I'm really ashamed to ask this of you,
我真的很不好意思開口
but I have a favor to ask.
但是不得不請你幫個忙
What are you doing here?
有什麼事嗎？
Section Chief Haneda.
羽田課長
Why did you deny the loan for Koda Sangyo?
你為什麼拒絕貸款給幸田產業？
-What? -And on the day of the settlement.
-什麼？ -而且還在結算日
Their payment may bounce.
他們的款項可能跳票
Wait. I haven't received the proposal for Koda Sangyo yet.
等等，我沒有收到幸田產業的提案書
-What? -Today's the settlement day?
-什麼？ -今天是結算日？
You didn't know?
你不知道這件事？
Mr. Itami didn't turn in his proposal document?
伊丹先生沒有遞交提案書？
No, he did not.
他沒有
Koda Sangyo's account
幸田產業的帳戶
has an insufficient fund of 47 million yen.
短缺四千七百萬日圓的資金
At this rate, this check will really bounce.
照這個樣子真的會跳票
-Where's Itami? -Not picking up.
-伊丹在哪裡？ -沒接電話
Section Chief Fushimi, how long can you wait to process that?
伏見課長，這件事你能等多久？
I can wait until 4:30 p.m.
我可以等到4點半
Only two more hours.
只剩下兩個小時
Hello, President Koda. This is Soma.
喂，幸田社長，我是相馬
Our bank can wait until 4:30 p.m. to process the check.
那些支票銀行可以等到4點半
I can get up to ten million yen
我可以籌到一千萬
but getting the rest by 4:30 p.m. may be
可是要在4點半前籌足剩下的
impossible for us.
不可能
I see. I will call back again.
我知道了，我會再跟你聯絡
Where's the branch manager?
分行經理在哪裡？
He's heading to Kumamoto to tour Nakamaru Denki's factory.
他正前往熊本市參觀中丸電氣的工廠
-He's probably on his flight right now. -I see.
-現在可能正在飛機上 -這樣子啊
Let's have Finance at headquarters approve an emergency loan.
我們請總部的融資部通過緊急貸款
-You can do that? -It'll be a stretch, but yes.
-可以這樣做嗎？ -可以
-That's our only option. -But…
-那是我們唯一的選擇 -可是
Koda Sangyo's financial statements
幸田產業的財報
showed that their business is going well.
顯示他們生意進展順利
It's wrong to deny their loan
駁回五千萬日圓貸款
for 50 million yen!
是錯誤的決定
At this rate, Koda Sangyo will go bankrupt, right?
照這樣下去，幸田產業會破產嗎？
Yes.
是
A company is about to go bankrupt
只因為我們的一位員工
just because of one employee.
就讓一個公司即將破產
That's definitely wrong.
這絕對有問題
-Look for the proposal document. -Yes!
-找出提案書！ -是！
-Here's the temporary password. -Thanks.
-這是臨時密碼 -謝謝
It's not here.
不在這裡
PROPOSAL DOCUMENT
（提案書）
Here it is.
找到了
What is this?
這是什麼？
It's unfinished!
根本沒完成！
-Let's make one. -What?
-我來擬一份 -什麼？
-A new proposal document. -It's too late now.
-新的提案書 -來不及了
We won't know until we try.
試過才知道
-We have two more hours. -With only two hours…
-還有兩個小時 -只剩兩個小時
President Koda hasn't given up yet.
幸田社長還沒有放棄
So we have to do all that we can.
必須用盡所有我們可能的辦法
You're right. Saito, can you…
你說的對，齋藤，你來
-No, please let me do it. -What?
-不，請讓我來 -什麼？
I was in charge of Koda Sangyo ten years ago.
十年前，幸田產業是我負責的
-Really? Okay, please do it. -Okay.
-是這樣嗎？那就請你來吧 -是
I'll help.
我來幫忙
-Please examine all of the statements. -Yes.
-請檢視所有財報 -是
Hanasaki, call Finance at headquarters.
花咲，打電話給總部的融資部
-Get an appointment with the director. -Okay.
-預約部長的時間 -好
Hello, I'm Hanasaki from Branch Inspection.
喂，我是稽核班的花咲
Is Director Nishino there?
請問西野部長在嗎？
In a meeting… until when?
在開會啊…到幾點？
I see. Which meeting room is it?
是，在哪間會議室呢？
I understand. Thank you.
我知道了，謝謝
Bye.
再見
I'll go to headquarters.
我去總部，這樣他一出會議室
-He can look at the files once he's out. -Okay.
-就能看檔案 -好
-We'll send it soon.
-我們會很快送出去 -好的
CUSTOMER'S FINANCIAL STATEMENT
（客戶財務報告）
Okay. That looks good.
可以，看起來不錯
-Mr. Soma. -Okay, let's put it together.
-相馬先生 -好，我們整合起來
Okay.
好的
I'll head to headquarters too.
我也去總部
-Okay. -Please take care of the rest.
-好的 -交給你們了
Oh…
啊！
Excuse me. Where is Director Nishino of Finance?
抱歉，請問融資部的西野部長在哪？
I'm Nishino. Who are you?
我是西野，妳是哪位？
I'm Hanasaki from Branch Inspection.
我是稽核班的花咲
There is a case here.
有一件緊急貸款案
-It needs an immediate loan approval. -What?
-需要您立即核准 -什麼？
That's ridiculous. Why does headquarters have to clean up
太荒謬了，為什麼總部
the mess made by the branch?
要收拾分行的爛攤子？
Um… this is not the time to be talking about these issues.
現在不是討論總部與分行
-Those at the branch and headquarters. -What?
-責任歸屬的時候 -什麼？
An honest company that has been with us for over ten years is about to
一間與我們往來超過十年的可靠公司
go bankrupt because of our mistake.
即將因為我們的失誤而破產
Please help us.
請您幫忙
-Hello. -It's Shinjuku's Branch Manager Tokuyama.
-是 -是新宿分行的德山經理
-Put him through. -Okay.
-接過來 -好的
Hello.
是
Yes, she's here…
對，她在這裡
I see. I got it.
這樣啊，我知道了
I'll look at the proposal document.
我會看提案書
Thank you very much.
非常感謝
But whether I approve or not.
但會不會核准
-That will depend on the proposal. -Yes, sir.
-就看提案書了 -是
LOAN PROPOSAL DOCUMENT
（貸款提案書）
Okay. This should be good enough.
好，這樣應該可以
-Send this right away. -Yes, sir.
-立刻傳給總部 -是
ELECTRONIC LOAN SYSTEM
（電子融資系統）
-Hello. -Hanasaki.
-喂 -花咲
We just sent it.
我們剛剛傳出去了
Okay. Excuse me.
我知道了，我掛電話了
Hanasaki.
花咲
Section Chief Haneda.
羽田課長
We uploaded the proposal document. Please check it.
提案書已經上傳，請過目
ELECTRONIC LOAN SYSTEM
（電子融資系統）
PROPOSAL NUMBER
（提案書號碼）
We'll discuss this right away.
我們立刻討論
I'll call soon.
我很快會打電話過去
-Thank you very much. -Thank you.
-麻煩您了 -麻煩了
How was it?
怎麼樣？
We did all we could.
我們盡全力了
We just have to wait.
現在只能等待
We'll get ready to process it.
-一有消息，我們做好準備立刻處理 -是
-Good work. -Not at all.
-辛苦了 -不會
But why didn't Mr. Itami
可是為什麼伊丹先生
turn in the proposal document?
不遞交提案書呢？
All I can think of is that he didn't want to finance Koda Sangyo.
我能想到的是 他不想提供貸款給幸田產業
He didn't turn it in on purpose?
他故意不交出去？
That idiot! Why would he…
那個笨蛋，他為何要這樣？
Did he have a personal grudge against them?
他和他們有過節嗎？
So he's somehow linked with Mr. Koda?
他和幸田先生有某種關聯嗎？
There's something that I've been wondering about.
我一直在想一件事
What is it?
什麼事？
Itami was in the Sales Division
伊丹來這裡之後
for about two months after he came here.
在營業課待過大約兩個月
-I see. -It happened then.
-是 -那個時候
Itami processed the wrong amount on a transfer slip, and that customer
伊丹弄錯一張匯款單的金額
was President Koda.
那位客戶就是幸田社長
This is not good. This ended up causing trouble for our customers.
那樣不行 最後會造成我們客戶的困擾
I see.
我知道了
Then please fill this out. We will deposit the rest.
那麼請填好這個，我們會存入剩下的
Deposit the rest? This was your mistake,
存入剩下的？這是你的錯誤
so you should process the correction.
你應該做更正處理
But this is easier.
但是這麼做比較容易
You're not going to apologize?
你不打算道歉嗎？
It's only 500,000 yen.
才五十萬日圓
Are you serious?
你是認真的嗎？
What? He's holding a grudge just for something like that?
他為了那種事心懷怨恨？
That's most likely it…
很可能是那樣
Itami is someone that can't apologize to people.
伊丹是那種不道歉的人
He's too proud.
他太高傲
He's probably never had anyone get mad at him before.
大概從來沒有人對他生氣吧？
He's an elite with a sheltered upbringing so he's not thick-skinned.
他是從小受到保護的菁英份子 所以臉皮不夠厚
But even so…
就算這樣也不能…
Mr. Koda is here.
幸田先生到了
I was only able to get ten million yen.
我只籌到一千萬日圓
We asked headquarters for an emergency loan for 50 million.
我們向總部請求五千萬日圓緊急貸款
-Really? -Yes.
-真的嗎？ -是，不過
But we don't know if it'll make it in time.
不知道是否來得及
I see… but…
我知道了，不過
-Thank you very much. -Not at all.
-非常感謝你 -沒什麼
Mr. Koda, please sit down.
幸田先生，請坐
Yes.
是
Thank you.
非常感謝！
-Please process it. -Yes.
-請立刻處理 -是
LOAN
（融資）
LOAN CERTIFICATE NUMBER
（融資認證號碼）
PROCESS
（執行）
It's done!
完成了！
The check won't bounce.
不會跳票了！
-All right! -We did it!
-太好了！ -成功了！
-We did it. -Thank you!
-我們做到了 -非常感謝！
Yes.
是
What's going on?
什麼事啊？
-What were you doing? -Visiting customers.
-你做了什麼？ -拜訪客戶
I don't care about that.
那個我不在乎
Why didn't you submit Koda Sangyo's proposal document?
為什麼你沒有遞交 幸田產業的提案書？
Today was the settlement day.
今天是結算日
What? Was it today?
啊，是今天嗎？
You're saying you didn't know?
你是說你不知道嗎？
I must have forgot.
我一定是忘了
And what happened?
出了什麼事？
We were able to avoid the check from bouncing.
我們避免了支票跳票
I see.
這樣啊
"I see"? That's all you can say?
“這樣啊”，你就只說這個？
A company was about to go down because of you.
一間公司因為你差點倒閉
I told you, I just forgot.
我說了，我只不過是忘記
I'm working on a big contract, so I've got my hands full.
我正在處理一個大合約，忙得不得了
Is it true that you really forgot?
你真的是忘記嗎？
Yeah.
是啊
Is that so?
真是那樣？
You had a personal grudge against President Koda,
你對幸田社長心懷怨恨
and that's why you didn't want to finance his company. Right?
所以才不想給他的公司貸款，是嗎？
What are you saying?
你在胡說什麼啊？
This is a half-written proposal document that was saved
這是存在你電腦裡
in your computer.
寫了一半的提案書
PROPOSAL DOCUMENT
（提案書）
You looked?
-你怎麼能擅自看？ -所以你記得這個？
"Unstable company with no future prospect.
“公司不穩定，未來無前景
Low profit, with lots of competition.
獲利低，競爭對手眾多
May not last the next three years."
可能撐不過接下來的三年”
It's written as if to prevent them from getting a loan.
這種寫法就像是要避免他們取得貸款
But you must have thought
但是你一定想過
that your boss would still approve the loan.
你的上司還是會核可貸款
That's why you purposely didn't turn in the proposal document,
所以你才刻意不遞交提案書
to make it seem like there was no loan proposal at all.
讓它看起來根本沒有貸款提案書
You talked to President Koda as if the approval was denied, and turned down
你對幸田社長說成好像貸款被拒
the loan on your own accord,
你自行拒絕貸款
without telling your boss.
卻沒有告訴你的上司
Did you think you'd be able to pull it off?
你認為你能夠得逞嗎？
That's just your imagination.
那只是你的推論
You're an outsider, so stay quiet.
你是局外人，請你閉嘴
No, I won't stay quiet.
我不會閉嘴的
You started this proposal five days ago.
你五天前開始寫這個提案書
It clearly says on here
上面清楚寫著
that the settlement day is today.
今天就是結算日
So let me ask again.
我再問你一次
Is it true that you really forgot?
你真的是忘記嗎？
Our mistake has
我們的錯誤造成你很大的麻煩
caused you lots of trouble. We're very sorry.
我們感到萬分抱歉
It's okay. Please raise your head.
別這樣，請抬起頭來
Apologize to him!
跟他道歉！
It all worked out.
事情都解決了
You didn't go bankrupt.
你沒有破產
Hey you…
你這個…
-Hey! -Mr. Haneda!
-喂！ -羽田先生！
Are you sure you want to do that?
你確定你想那麼做？
I can easily get rid of a low-level banker like you.
我輕易就能除掉你們這種低階行員！
What?
怎樣？
How can you say such a thing?
你怎麼說得出這種話？
When you caused this trouble.
這個麻煩是你造成的
What? It's not my fault.
說什麼？這不是我的錯
A small company that can't survive
一個沒有五千萬就無法生存的小公司
without a 50-million-yen loan is bound to
注定會破產
go bankrupt sooner or later.
只是遲早的事
Don't you know that?
妳不知道嗎？
Are you an idiot?
妳是笨蛋嗎？
With all due respect…
恕我直言
you are the damn idiot.
你才是可惡的笨蛋
Have you ever thought about
你從來沒想過
how your single proposal can bankrupt one company
你的一份提案書可以讓一間公司破產
and leave many employees without a job.
讓許多員工失去工作
Among those employees are people
那些員工
supporting their family while paying their mortgages.
有人要在付貸款的同時 還要支撐家計
The happiness of those people
那些人的幸福
was about to be taken away by your stupid pride.
差點被你愚蠢的自尊剝奪
That's wrong!
那是不對的
Stop this nonsense!
廢話少說！
Do you know who you're speaking to?
妳知道妳在跟誰說話嗎？
I do!
我知道
You've only been here for four years,
你只在這裡待了四年
so you're just a rookie banker who has
只不過是一個菜鳥行員
no knowledge of the bank!
對銀行一無所知
Mr. Itami, in the future
伊丹先生，你未來
you may become a manager over many people.
可能會成為管理很多人的社長
But right now,
但是此刻
you're a nobody!
你只是無名小卒！
Dad, choose where you want to go from here.
爸，從裡面選一個你想去的地方
-What? -Hot spring.
-什麼？ -溫泉
You wanted to go, right?
你不是說你想去？
But that's when you get a husband.
可是那是等妳找到丈夫之後
But I don't have one.
但是沒人選啊，沒辦法吧？
-So come with me. -But I'm in the red this month.
-所以跟我去吧 -但是我這個月是赤字
I'll take you, since it's Father's Day.
我帶你去，因為是父親節
What?
什麼？
-I'll be off. -Okay, bye.
-我走了 -好，再見
That girl.
這個女兒啊
Don't think that you can get on my good side with…
沒想到妳會替我想…
Natural hot spring from the source?
天然溫泉之源？
Chairman Itami's son
伊丹會長的公子
will get a strong disciplinary action, right?
會受到嚴重紀錄懲處，是吧？
Yeah.
沒錯
It can't be helped, since he did something unacceptable.
那也沒辦法 因為他做了不被接受的事
But will that be all right?
可是那樣沒問題嗎？
The Ginza Redevelopment Project.
那個銀座再開發計畫
What if it goes down the drain?
萬一付諸東流了怎麼辦？
Branch Inspection
那兩個稽核員
did something unnecessary again.
又做了沒有必要的事
This is the result of them saving one company.
結果是他們拯救了一間公司
Well that's true, but…
那是沒錯，可是
I heard that Chairman Itami
我聽說伊丹會長
really dotes on his son.
非常溺愛他兒子
I…
我呢
don't think they did anything wrong.
不認為他們做錯任何事情
Today's inspection is Hamamatsu Branch.
今天稽核的是濱松分行
Hamamatsu is famous for eels, right?
濱松的鰻魚很有名，對吧？
How can you be so cheerful?
妳怎麼能這麼開心啊？
Why?
怎麼了嗎？
I'm losing my appetite
一想到真藤本部長
thinking of how Mr. Shindo must be so mad about Itami Junior.
一定對伊丹少東的事很生氣 我就沒胃口了
Then would you have let Koda Sangyo go bankrupt?
那麼你會讓幸田產業破產嗎？
Of course not.
當然不會
Then we had no choice.
那我們就沒得選擇了
That's true, but…
是沒錯
Hey, it's best to eat eel when you
對了，你沒胃口
don't have an appetite.
吃鰻魚最好了
-Yes, it's very nutritious. -All right, let's go Mr. Soma.
-是沒錯，鰻魚營養豐富 -我們走吧，相馬先生
You're so positive.
你真樂觀
Eel, eel…
鰻魚…
HR is asking about the disciplinary action
人事部在詢問對伊丹清一郎的
for Seiichiro Itami.
紀律處分
How should I answer them?
我該怎麼回答他們呢？
Have HR take care of him.
要人事部把這件事壓下來
What?
什麼？
Once the dust settles, send him to a different branch.
等塵埃落定，送他去別的分行
But then that wouldn't be
可是那就不是
a disciplinary action.
紀律處分了
Is there an issue?
你有意見嗎？
A company called Koda Sangyo received a loan of 50 million yen.
一家叫幸田產業的公司 獲得五千萬日圓的貸款
They didn't go bankrupt either.
他們也沒有破產
It's all about the result.
結果就是一切
That's how a bank works.
這就是銀行
Oh, I want to eat whitebait too.
我也想吃銀魚
No, let's go with eel.
不要，我們吃鰻魚
-Whitebait. -Eel.
-銀魚 -鰻魚
FINALLY THE LAST EPISODE
（完結篇）
10,000 people's payroll data is lost.
一萬名員工的薪資資料不見了！
Lost?
不見了？
This is a big problem.
這可是大問題
-I'm very sorry. -How are you handling the press?
-我非常抱歉 -媒體是怎麼回事？
What are you guys doing?
你們在搞什麼？
Where did the data go?
薪資資料去哪了？
Everyone here can be dispatched somewhere.
這裡的每個人都會被調職
You'll get dispatched somewhere.
妳肯定會被調職
With all due respect…
恕我直言
It's wrong to blame things on innocent people.
把責任推給無辜的人是不對的
-Shut up! -No, I will not.
-閉嘴！ -我不要！
Dissolve Branch Inspection.
稽核班將會解散
Hanasaki, you're not wrong.
花咲，妳沒有錯
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita
字幕翻譯：李怡樸